Episode 9    My Big Sister Has Changed
It's been a while, huh?
Urami?
Yeah.
Hey, Big Sister...
Yeah?
Menacing
Who is that?
Kii!
Clueless
Huh?
K-Kii?!
Kii-ii-ii!
Just someone I know!
What is your name?
Fu—
Flustered
M-Mudo, sir.
Mudo-kun?
What's an average Gekko foot soldier
doin' in my daughter's...
in Reaper Princess's room?
Well...
H-He was helping me study!
I have a test coming up!
You great oaf!
What's a great soldier of
Gekko need to be studyin' for?
All ya need's a wicked heart and
a drive toward world domination!
And what's happenin' in this room, here?
Look at all this froo-froo crap!
You're not even puttin' up a Gekko flag!
Lifetime Gekko Soldier
Hey! Stop it, Dad!
You're ruinin' the atmosphere!
Don't you talk that way to—
Ouch!
Shock
A-Are these... Super Bosslar-kun Dolls?!
The legendary dolls that I longed for so
desperately when I was still in action...
Just left lyin' around...
There's just nowhere to put them.
Bosslar-sama! I beg your forgiveness!
Sorry. This is just kind
of how my father is...
Don't worry. It's no problem.
And I have to say, your father is very—
Oh, right!
Listen up, Desumi!
I heard you turned down
your monster promotion!
I spent my entire life as a
low-level Gekko soldier...
I can't tell ya how proud
I was seein' my daughter
rising through the ranks so quickly...
What's goin' through your head
turnin' that down, you great oaf?
If you don't mind my saying so, sir.
Desumi-san only reached that decision
after long, hard consideration.
I ask that you do not chastise her for—
Smash
F-Mudo!
What would you know about my sister?
Maybe you oughta stay outta
our business, outsider.
A-Are you all right, Fudo?
Well, she's definitely your little sister...
Full of terrifying potential.
I appreciate the sentiment, Fudo.
But you really shouldn't speak
up about my life like that.
Urami is...
Love Big Sister
I love my big sister. I love my
big sister. I love my big sister.
Love Big Sister
Let's just say she's got
a serious sister complex.
Love Big Sister
I see. I'll be careful.
Here's the best way to blast away fatigue!
The brand-new energy drink, Power 1!
Red Gelato recommends Power 1!
With just one drink, you can
blast away Gekko and exhaustion!
You annoyin' little brat!
Reaper Princess is gonna tear
out your guts any day now!
What? Why?!
Just kidding!
Your humor is adorable.
We gotta get rid of Gelato 5
as soon as possible!
Desumi! Quit wastin' your time on studies!
Spend it trainin' from now on instead!
In a year's time, you'll be
finished with high school,
and you'll be able to
focus on Gekko full-time!
You got that, Desumi?
Yes.
I hope we can go together, Fudo.
I know we will.
S-Sir!
I have a request to make of you!
Yeah?
Desumi-san wishes to go to college.
I beg you, allow her!
Fudo...
I thought somethin' strange
was goin' on here.
The sister I knew wasn't
all carefree like this.
She should be the strongest
and most ruthless person ever.
And you ruined her.
My sister was invincible.
Give her back!
Stop, Urami.
Let me go.
Stop it.
Tearful...
I hate you, Big Sister!
Sir! I beg you, give Desumi-san
permission to go to university!
This is a family matter, son.
You'd better stay out of it.
I will not be silent!
All right.
You give me no choice!
Get up.
Menacing
I'll teach you a lesson in the
Gekko way of doin' things.
Sir!
Let us begin, Mudo-kun!
W-Wait a mi—
Kii!
I didn't do any—
Do you see, Mudo-kun?
This is the art of defeat.
Art?
"How spectacularly can one lose a fight?"
I spent my years with this organization
working to refine this one skill!
But I don't think you understand
the pride I take in it.
I do.
Mudo-kun...
You truly understand?
Yes.
Gleek!
Gleek
No Artistry
Gwah!
Gwaaaaah!
Artistry
Others have laughed at that skill.
But I always believed it was
worth devoting myself to.
I will not be silent!
I can tell that you, too, are prepared
to devote yourself to a single cause.
You seem like a young man
with a lot of promise.
Desumi. I'm borrowin' your shower.
S-Sure...
We can discuss the university
thing another time.
See ya later, Desumi.
Look after Urami tomorrow, would ya?
I'm sorry about all that, Fudo.
I got you mixed up in a
complicated situation.
Easily dealt with, if it means
we can go to university together.
You really are very dashing.
Fudo, thank you for everything.
Of course!
What's she lookin' like that for?
I don't wanna see her lookin' like that!
I'll never accept that
man's presence in her life!
Love After World Domination!
Five
Years
Ago
Hey, hey! Wait up, Urami!
What's the matter, Urami?
Look at her! Urami the Loner!
C'mon, tell us off!
Bet she can't!
She's just a little emo who can't
talk louder than a mumble!
Desumi!
Crap! Beat it, guys!
Candy Shop
Chikugo
Don't cry, Urami.
Here. Want an ice pop?
Candy Shop
Chikugo
Get strong, Urami.
Strength is what you need to survive.
Right.
Present
Day
To Mt. Takao Entrance
Yesterday was great!
I loved your room!
Bring it on,
any time!
Grr
Grr...
What's with you? It's like ya
been in a bad mood all morning.
I ain't in no bad mood.
Hey, you sure this's where you wanna go?
I don't think it's worth sendin' Dad
home early and stickin' around for.
What's the big deal?
I just want to check out the place
I'm gonna start workin' next year.
Salute Reaper Princess!
Welcome, Reaper Princess!
That's my big sister!
When she's outside she
acts all weak an' casual,
but inside the organization's walls,
she's totally intimidatin'!
What do I always tell you?
I really don't like getting
the full royal treatment...
Just say "hello there," okay?
I'm not sure we can really...
Big Sister...
More importantly, do I look
any different today?
Well...
Oh, perhaps you seem a bit more
bloodthirsty than usual!
C'mon, notice the new hair!
Come over here.
Is that how you always act in
front of your subordinates?
I guess so, more or less...
Pathetic.
What's got you in such a bad mood?
Reaper Princess's little sister, eh?
Y-Yes. I'll be out of
junior high next year.
I hope to join Gekko then!
I fear Reaper Princess has
set the bar very high.
I hope you'll work hard to vault it!
Y-Yes! I will!
If you're related to Reaper Princess,
you must be pretty talented.
Gekko will be fortunate to have you.
Even the rest of the Princess
series respect her.
My big sister really is—
Urami! You like popcorn?
I hear a new place just
opened up in Harajuku!
Let's go!
Wait!
Big Sister—
I wanna try it out before I eat
it with Fudo—I mean, Mudo.
And who wants to hang around
this musty old place?
Speechless
I apologize for my sister!
That's
pretty
typical,
actually
Here, it's frozen popcorn!
No, thank you.
It looks great on you, Urami!
Seriously, no thank you.
I'll take it!
Thank you!
I wonder if he'd like this outfit!
Mudo has one of these!
And he says this one's really convenient!
Oh, this one too!
Caramellato
Strawberry
Banana Cream
Chocolate Banana
Silky
Banana Cream
Strawberry
Almond Cream
We can also try some crêpes—
I'm leaving.
H-Hey, Urami!
I mean it, what's with ya?
The sister I looked up to is gone now.
Urami?
You look like a total weakling now!
W-Wait, Urami!
Urami!
Found Urami the Loner!
Nowhere to be, huh, emo girl?
Whoops! Couldn't see ya with that
black cloud hangin' over ya!
Shut up.
What? You say somethin'?
Couldn't hear ya!
She can't even talk back
without her big sister around.
Total emo!
Urami ain't left her room yet?
No, an' it's been a whole week.
She must be so sad to have
her sister away in Tokyo.
Reaper Princess appears before
our Gelato 5 once more!
We've been waitin' for ya, Desumi-sensei!
Hooray! Hooray!
Go, Big Sis!
Darn it, five on one ain't fair!
She needs backup! What're those
oafish foot soldiers thinkin'?
You hear that, Urami?
We lost again today!
But your big sister stayed
on her feet to the end!
Urami! Your sister's
workin' hard again today!
Urami! Your sister's gotten
even stronger than before!
Urami! Your sister was the top
performer again this month!
Isn't that somethin', Urami?
Your sister's finally
been promoted to monster!
Urami...
I wanna be like my big sister.
My big sister was the one thing
that kept me goin' in life.
But she used to be so awesome...
and now, she's changed.
She met that strange man here
in the city, an' he ruined her.
Hey, you cryin'?
Dumped by your man?
Come hang out with me and forget that jerk.
Hang on, man. She seem a little young to you?
Who cares? She's a cutie.
C'mon, let's go!
Let me go.
Hey, did she just mumble something?
What are you, some kind of emo kid?
Yeah, looks totally emo to me!
Bet she can't even hold
a proper conversation.
Hello!
You hear me?
Nowhere to be, huh, emo girl?
Total emo!
Who are you supposed to be?
Big Sister...
Don't cry, Urami.
Here. Want a crêpe?
I think... we got bigger
things to worry about...
Hey, it's fine.
You said you think I look weak, didn't you?
But I'm actually the strongest
I've been in my life!
C'mon, don't ignore us.
That's how you make us mad.
We might look nice, but we're real bad guys.
It seems I don't have to hold back, then.
Better be careful.
I'm the real bad guy here.
Fall in love, Urami.
Love is what you need to survive.
That ain't what you used to say.
You'll understand, some day.
Yeah, right.
I'd rather not understand that.
The crêpe is good.
My big sister has changed.
She's lost her edge, become soft and girly.
But I guess she ain't so bad that way.
But you...
You're a big problem.
I'm never gonna like you.
Desumi-san
Desumi-san!
Once I join Gekko,
you're the first one I'll purge.
Mwahaha...
Mwahahahaha!
Big Sister!
Big Sister...
Urami! Where are you?
Next episode: "Atop the Kokutei Moon."
Episode 10   Atop the Kokutei Moon
Big Sister... I love you.
Urami!